<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
    <id>com.onepassword.client</id>
    <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
    <name>1Password for Linux development preview</name>
    <summary>Password manager and secure wallet</summary>
    <description>
        <p>
        Search 1Password
        Searching is the fastest way to find what you need in 1Password.
        To search in 1Password, use the search field at the top of the window (Control-F).
        </p>
        <p>
        Switch vaults and accounts
        You can use vaults in 1Password to organize your items and share them with others. If you have multiple 1Password accounts, each account has its own vaults.
        To see only the vaults from one account, click the account or collection at the top of the sidebar and choose the account.
        To view items in a specific vault, click the account or collection at the top of the sidebar and choose the account where the vault is located. Then click the vault in the sidebar.
        </p>
        <p>
        Organize your vaults into collections
        You can use collections to group and organize your vaults, even across multiple accounts. If you have multiple 1Password accounts, the Everything collection shows all the vaults in your unlocked accounts.
        To add a new collection, click the account or collection at the top of the sidebar and choose Manage Collections. Select the vaults to include, then name the collection.
        </p>
        <p>
        See who has access to an item
        If you share vaults with others, you can see who has access to an item. Click the people icon above the item’s title to see a list of people and groups who have access to it.
        If you don’t see the people icon, then only you have access to the item.
        </p>
        <p>
        Use Watchtower
        Watchtower tells you about password breaches and other security problems on the websites you have saved in 1Password. Click Watchtower in the sidebar to get a report for the current account or collection.
        </p>
        <p>
        Enlarge passwords
        You can temporarily enlarge a password to make it easier to see while entering it on another device or reading it aloud.
        To enlarge a password, hover over it. Then click and choose Show in Large Type.
        </p>
        <p>
        Lock 1Password
        When you’re done using 1Password, you can lock it. To lock 1Password, click the account or collection at the top of the sidebar and choose Lock (Control-Shift-L). Unlock 1Password again by entering your account password.
        </p>
        <p>
        Manage your settings
        To change your settings:
            <ol>
                <li>Open and unlock 1Password.</li>
                <li>Click the account or collection at the top of the sidebar and choose Settings.</li>
                <li>1Password will open a JSON-formatted settings file (~/.config/1Password/settings/settings.json) in your default text editor. Edit the file to add or change settings. </li>
                <li>Close and save the file. Your changes will take effect immediately.</li>
            </ol>
        </p>
        <p>To learn more, visit: https://support.1password.com/cs/getting-started-linux/</p>
    </description>
    <categories>
        <category>Utility</category>
    </categories>
    <url type="homepage">https://support.1password.com/cs/getting-started-linux/</url>
    <url type="faq">https://support.1password.com/cs/getting-started-linux/</url>
    <releases>
        <release version="0.8.0-22506" date="2020-08-05" type="development"/>
    </releases>
    <project_license>LicenseRef-1Password-Proprietary</project_license>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <image type="source"> https://com-agilebits-users.s3.amazonaws.com/dave/1password-linux-hero-nonscaled-web-iNFpMV172f7S.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
</component>
